# Raghad Malallah



raghadmalallah@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/raghad-malallah



+1 619-733-9149



https://github.com/Raghadmalallah

# Summary

Creative graphic designer/ Web Developer with innovative ideas and a unique approach to visuals. More than ten years of experience developing designs for print media, online websites, and advertising. Solid understanding of marketing principles and advertising techniques. Great attention to detail and a talent for creating memorable visual designs. Enthusiastic team player and committed to delivering top results on time and within the budget. Passion for keeping clients satisfied with each project.

Experienced UI developer trained in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, and Bootstrap.

Experienced UX design trained with Adobe Creative Suite.

# **Experience**



## Senior Graphic Designer

No name printing and sign

Apr 2019 - Aug 2021 (2 years 5 months)

Maintained brand identity across multiple brands. Generated concepts and followed through to production. Designed everything from billboards to e-blasts, web ads, magazine ads, print collateral, signage, apparel, brochures, web assets, POP displays, special projects and more. Upheld industry standard file management systems. Excellent written and verbal communication skills. Fluent in the adobe suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign) as well as office programs, photography and retouching, hand drawing skills and more.



# **Graphic Design Consultant**

IOM - UN Migration

Aug 2014 - Feb 2017 (2 years 7 months)

Created luxury branding and marketing materials that adhered to established brand standards. Materials included digital brochures, posters, magazine ads, shelf talkers, sell sheets, note cards, envelopes, packaging, PowerPoint presentations, as well as various web and social media materials.

#### **Education**



# Arab Community College

Associate's Degree, Graphic Design 2005 - 2007

#### **Licenses & Certifications**



## UCSD FULL STACK FLEX WEB DEVEOLPMENT

#### Skills

HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • Node.js • Web Development • Web Design • Adobe Creative Suite • Art Direction • Digital Printing • Product Photography

# **Honors & Awards**



Certificate of Achievement - Clarence jazmagy memorial award for excellence in photography